[
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "egoist",
        "answer": "believes in self advancement"
      },
      {
        "question": "egotist",
        "answer": "talks about accomplishments"
      },
      {
        "question": "altruist",
        "answer": "is interested in the welfare of others"
      },
      {
        "question": "introvert",
        "answer": "turns thoughts inward"
      },
      {
        "question": "extrovert",
        "answer": "turns thoughts outward"
      },
      {
        "question": "ambivert",
        "answer": "turns thoughts both inward and outward"
      },
      {
        "question": "misanthrope",
        "answer": "hates people"
      },
      {
        "question": "misogynist",
        "answer": "hates women"
      },
      {
        "question": "misogamist",
        "answer": "hates marriage"
      },
      {
        "question": "ascetic",
        "answer": "does not pursue pleasures of the flesh"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Is an egoist selfish?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is modesty one of the characteristics of the egoist?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an altruist selfish?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an introvert pay much attention to himself?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an extrovert prefer solitude to companionship?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are most normal people ambiverts?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a misanthrope like people?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a misogynist enjoy the company of women?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an ascetic lead a life of luxury?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a misogamist try to avoid marriage?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Who lives a lonely, asture life?",
        "answer": "ascetic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Whose interests are turned outward?",
        "answer": "extrovert"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is supremely selfish?",
        "answer": "egoist"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who hates people?",
        "answer": "misanthrope"
      },
      {
        "question": "Whose interests are turned both inward and outward?",
        "answer": "ambivert"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is incredibly conceited?",
        "answer": "egotist"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is more interested in the welfare of others than in his own?",
        "answer": "altruist"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who hates women?",
        "answer": "misogynist"
      },
      {
        "question": "Whose interests are turned inward?",
        "answer": "introvert"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who hates marriage?",
        "answer": "misogamist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "ego",
        "answer": "one's concept of oneself"
      },
      {
        "question": "egocentric",
        "answer": "one who is excessively fixated on his own desires, needs, etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "altruism",
        "answer": "philosophy of putting another's welfare above one's own"
      },
      {
        "question": "to alternate",
        "answer": "to take one, skip one etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "to alter",
        "answer": "to change"
      },
      {
        "question": "altercation",
        "answer": "argument"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "egomaniacal",
        "answer": "morbidly, obsessively wrapped up in oneself"
      },
      {
        "question": "altruistic",
        "answer": "interested in the welfare of others"
      },
      {
        "question": "alternative",
        "answer": "a choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "alteration",
        "answer": "a change"
      },
      {
        "question": "alter ego",
        "answer": "one's other self"
      },
      {
        "question": "alternate (adj.)",
        "answer": "other possible"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Is rejection usually a blow to one's ego?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Are egocentric people easy to get along with?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an egomaniac have a normal personality?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are egomaniacal tendencies a sign of maturity?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is altruism a characteristic of selfish people?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are altruistic tendencies common to egoists?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an alternate plan necessarily inferior?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an alternative allow you some freedom of choice?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does alteration imply keeping things the same?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Do excitable people often engage in altercations?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is your alter ego usually quite similar to yourself?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "one's other self",
        "answer": "alter ego"
      },
      {
        "question": "to change",
        "answer": "alter"
      },
      {
        "question": "a heated dispute",
        "answer": "altercation"
      },
      {
        "question": "excessively, morbidly obsessed with one's own needs, desires, or ambitions",
        "answer": "egomaniacal"
      },
      {
        "question": "unselfish; more interested in the welfare of others than in one's own",
        "answer": "altruistic"
      },
      {
        "question": "utterly involved with oneself; self-centered",
        "answer": "egocentric"
      },
      {
        "question": "a choice",
        "answer": "alternative"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who substitutes for another",
        "answer": "alternate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "ambidextrous",
        "answer": "capable of using both hands with equal skill"
      },
      {
        "question": "dextrous",
        "answer": "skillful"
      },
      {
        "question": "sinister",
        "answer": "evil, threatening"
      },
      {
        "question": "gauche",
        "answer": "awkward"
      },
      {
        "question": "misanthropic",
        "answer": "hating mankind"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "anthropology",
        "answer": "study of human development"
      },
      {
        "question": "gynecology",
        "answer": "study of female ailments"
      },
      {
        "question": "monogamy",
        "answer": "system of only one marriage"
      },
      {
        "question": "bigamy",
        "answer": "illegal plurality of marriages"
      },
      {
        "question": "misogyny",
        "answer": "hatred of women"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "polygamy",
        "answer": "custom in which one man has many wives"
      },
      {
        "question": "misogamy",
        "answer": "hatred of marriage"
      },
      {
        "question": "asceticism",
        "answer": "devotion to a lonely and austere life"
      },
      {
        "question": "philanthropy",
        "answer": "love of mankind"
      },
      {
        "question": "adroitness",
        "answer": "skill, cleverness"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "polygynist",
        "answer": "male with a plurality of wives"
      },
      {
        "question": "polyandrist",
        "answer": "female with a plurality of husbands"
      },
      {
        "question": "anthropologist",
        "answer": "student of the development of mankind"
      },
      {
        "question": "gynecologist",
        "answer": "women's doctor"
      },
      {
        "question": "philanthropist",
        "answer": "one who engages in charitable works"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Can ambidextrous people use either the left or right hand equally well?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Should a surgeon be manually dexterous?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a sinister-looking person frightening?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is gaucherie a social asset?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an adroit speaker likely to be a successful lawyer?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a student of anthropology interested in primitive tribes?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a gynecologist have more male than female patients?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is monogamy the custom in Western countries?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a misogamist likely to show tendencies toward polygamy?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a bigamist breaking the law?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a philanthropist generally altruistic?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a misanthropist enjoy human relationships?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a misogynist enjoy female companionship?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are unmarried people necessarily misogamous?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are bachelors necessarily misogamous?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is asceticism compatible with luxurious living and the pursuit of pleasure?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a polyandrist have more than one husband?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "philosophy of living austerely",
        "answer": "asceticism"
      },
      {
        "question": "hatred of women",
        "answer": "misogyny"
      },
      {
        "question": "hatred of marriage",
        "answer": "misogamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "hatred of mankind",
        "answer": "misanthropy"
      },
      {
        "question": "skillful",
        "answer": "dexterous"
      },
      {
        "question": "awkward",
        "answer": "gauche"
      },
      {
        "question": "evil, threatening",
        "answer": "sinister"
      },
      {
        "question": "describing hatred of women (adj.)",
        "answer": "misogynistic"
      },
      {
        "question": "skill",
        "answer": "adroitness"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to hatred of marriage (adj.)",
        "answer": "misogamous"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to hatred of mankind (adj.)",
        "answer": "misanthropic"
      },
      {
        "question": "social custom of plural marriage",
        "answer": "polygamy, polyandry or polygyny"
      },
      {
        "question": "unlawful state of having more than one spouse",
        "answer": "bigamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "doctor specializing in female disorders",
        "answer": "gynecologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "custom of one marriage at a time",
        "answer": "monogamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who hates the human race",
        "answer": "misanthropist"
      },
      {
        "question": "able to use both hands with equal skill",
        "answer": "ambidextrous"
      },
      {
        "question": "study of mankind",
        "answer": "anthropology"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who loves mankind",
        "answer": "philanthropist"
      },
      {
        "question": "skill in the use of both hands",
        "answer": "ambidexterity"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Mcq",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Puts selfish desires first",
        "answer": "egoist",
        "options": [
          "egoist",
          "egotist",
          "altruist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Is self-analytical",
        "answer": "introvert",
        "options": [
          "extrovert",
          "introvert",
          "ambivert"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Hates women",
        "answer": "misogynist",
        "options": [
          "misogamist",
          "misanthrope",
          "misogynist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "One's other self",
        "answer": "alter ego",
        "options": [
          "altercation",
          "alter ego",
          "alteration"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Awkward, clumsy",
        "answer": "gauche",
        "options": [
          "adroit",
          "dexterous",
          "gauche"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Plural marriage as a custom",
        "answer": "polygamy",
        "options": [
          "bigamy",
          "polygamy",
          "monogamy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Study of human development",
        "answer": "anthropology",
        "options": [
          "asceticism",
          "philanthropy",
          "anthropology"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Plurality of husbands as a custom",
        "answer": "polyandry",
        "options": [
          "misogyny",
          "polygyny",
          "polyandry"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "ego",
        "answer": "self",
        "example": "egoist"
      },
      {
        "question": "alter",
        "answer": "other",
        "example": "alternative"
      },
      {
        "question": "verto",
        "answer": "to turn",
        "example": "introvert"
      },
      {
        "question": "misein",
        "answer": "to hate",
        "example": "misogynist"
      },
      {
        "question": "anthropos",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "example": "anthropologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "gyne",
        "answer": "woman",
        "example": "gynecologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "gamos",
        "answer": "marriage",
        "example": "bigamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "centrum",
        "answer": "center",
        "example": "egocentric"
      },
      {
        "question": "dexter",
        "answer": "right hand",
        "example": "dexterous"
      },
      {
        "question": "droit",
        "answer": "right hand",
        "example": "adroit"
      },
      {
        "question": "monos",
        "answer": "one",
        "example": "monogamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "andros",
        "answer": "male",
        "example": "polyandry"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "mental or emotional disturbances",
        "answer": "psychiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "nervous system",
        "answer": "neurologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "skin",
        "answer": "dermatologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "diagnosis; internal organs",
        "answer": "internist"
      },
      {
        "question": "infants",
        "answer": "pediatrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "female reproductive organs",
        "answer": "gynecologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "eyes",
        "answer": "ophthalmologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "heart",
        "answer": "cardiologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "pregnancy, childbirth",
        "answer": "obstetrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "skeletal system",
        "answer": "orthopedist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Is an internist an expert in diagnosis?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a gynecologist familiar with the female reproductive organs?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an obstetrician specialize in diseases of childhood?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a pediatrician deliver babies?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "If you had a skin disease, would you visit a dermatologist?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "If you had trouble with your vision would you visit an orthopedist?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an ophthalmologist an eye specialist?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a cardiologist treat bone fractures?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a neurologist a nerver specialist?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "If you were nervous, tense, overly anxious, contantly fearful for no apparent reasons, would psychiatrist be the specialist to see?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "for a suspected brain disorder",
        "answer": "neurologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "for a thorough internal checkup",
        "answer": "internist"
      },
      {
        "question": "if you have a skin disease",
        "answer": "dermatologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "if you have a heart problem",
        "answer": "cardiologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "if you are tense, fearful, insecure",
        "answer": "psychiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "if you are pregnant",
        "answer": "obstetrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "for some disorder of the female reproductive organs",
        "answer": "gynecologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "for a checkup for your two-month-old child",
        "answer": "pediatrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "for faulty vision",
        "answer": "ophthalmologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "for curvature of the spine",
        "answer": "orthopedist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "gynecology",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with women's diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "obstetrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the delivery of newborn infants"
      },
      {
        "question": "pediatrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the treatment of children"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedagogy",
        "answer": "principles of teaching"
      },
      {
        "question": "demagoguery",
        "answer": "stirring up discontent among the masses"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatology",
        "answer": "treatment of skin diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "taxidermy",
        "answer": "stuffing of skins of animals"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "hypodermic",
        "answer": "under the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "epidermis",
        "answer": "outer layer of skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "pachyderm",
        "answer": "elephant"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatitis",
        "answer": "inflammation of the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "ophthalmologist",
        "answer": "eye doctor"
      },
      {
        "question": "optometrist",
        "answer": "one who measures vision"
      },
      {
        "question": "optician",
        "answer": "lens grinder"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does pedagogy refer to teaching?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a lion a pachyderm?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is dermititis an inflammation of one of the limbs?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an opthalmologist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an optometrist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an optician prescribe glasses?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "gynecology",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with women's diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "obstetrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the delivery of newborn infants"
      },
      {
        "question": "pediatrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the treatment of children"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedagogy",
        "answer": "principles of teaching"
      },
      {
        "question": "demagoguery",
        "answer": "stirring up discontent among the masses"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatology",
        "answer": "treatment of skin diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "taxidermy",
        "answer": "stuffing of skins of animals"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "hypodermic",
        "answer": "under the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "epidermis",
        "answer": "outer layer of skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "pachyderm",
        "answer": "elephant"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatitis",
        "answer": "inflammation of the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "ophthalmologist",
        "answer": "eye doctor"
      },
      {
        "question": "optometrist",
        "answer": "one who measures vision"
      },
      {
        "question": "optician",
        "answer": "lens grinder"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does pedagogy refer to teaching?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a lion a pachyderm?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is dermititis an inflammation of one of the limbs?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an opthalmologist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an optometrist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an optician prescribe glasses?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "specialty of child delivery",
        "answer": "obstetrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "outer layer of skin",
        "answer": "epidermis"
      },
      {
        "question": "principles of teaching",
        "answer": "pedagogy"
      },
      {
        "question": "thick-skinned animal",
        "answer": "pachyderm"
      },
      {
        "question": "skin inflammation",
        "answer": "dermatitis"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who foments political discontent",
        "answer": "demagogue"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who sells optical equipment",
        "answer": "optician"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical graduate serving his apprenticeship",
        "answer": "intern"
      },
      {
        "question": "treatment of childhood diseases",
        "answer": "pediatrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "practice of stirring up political dissatisfaction for purely personal gain",
        "answer": "demagoguery"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who stuffs the skins of animals",
        "answer": "taxidermist"
      },
      {
        "question": "another title of ophthalmologist",
        "answer": "oculist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treatment of female ailments",
        "answer": "gynecology"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical specialty relating to diseases of the eye",
        "answer": "ophthalmology"
      },
      {
        "question": "one-lens eyeglass",
        "answer": "monocle"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the eye",
        "answer": "ocular"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who measures vision",
        "answer": "optometrist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "gynecology",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with women's diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "obstetrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the delivery of newborn infants"
      },
      {
        "question": "pediatrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with the treatment of children"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedagogy",
        "answer": "principles of teaching"
      },
      {
        "question": "demagoguery",
        "answer": "stirring up discontent among the masses"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatology",
        "answer": "treatment of skin diseases"
      },
      {
        "question": "taxidermy",
        "answer": "stuffing of skins of animals"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "hypodermic",
        "answer": "under the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "epidermis",
        "answer": "outer layer of skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "pachyderm",
        "answer": "elephant"
      },
      {
        "question": "dermatitis",
        "answer": "inflammation of the skin"
      },
      {
        "question": "ophthalmologist",
        "answer": "eye doctor"
      },
      {
        "question": "optometrist",
        "answer": "one who measures vision"
      },
      {
        "question": "optician",
        "answer": "lens grinder"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Does a treatise on obstetrics deal with childbirth?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does gynecology deal with the female reproductive organs?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is pediatrics concerned with the diseases of old age?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does pedagogy refer to teaching?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a pedagogue an expert teacher?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a demagogue interested in the welfare of the people?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a lion a pachyderm?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the epidermis one of the layers of the skin?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is dermititis an inflammation of one of the limbs?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a taxidermist a medical practitioner?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an opthalmologist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an optometrist a medical doctor?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an optician prescribe glasses?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "specialty of child delivery",
        "answer": "obstetrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "outer layer of skin",
        "answer": "epidermis"
      },
      {
        "question": "principles of teaching",
        "answer": "pedagogy"
      },
      {
        "question": "thick-skinned animal",
        "answer": "pachyderm"
      },
      {
        "question": "skin inflammation",
        "answer": "dermatitis"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who foments political discontent",
        "answer": "demagogue"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who sells optical equipment",
        "answer": "optician"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical graduate serving his apprenticeship",
        "answer": "intern"
      },
      {
        "question": "treatment of childhood diseases",
        "answer": "pediatrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "practice of stirring up political dissatisfaction for purely personal gain",
        "answer": "demagoguery"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who stuffs the skins of animals",
        "answer": "taxidermist"
      },
      {
        "question": "another title of ophthalmologist",
        "answer": "oculist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treatment of female ailments",
        "answer": "gynecology"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical specialty relating to diseases of the eye",
        "answer": "ophthalmology"
      },
      {
        "question": "one-lens eyeglass",
        "answer": "monocle"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the eye",
        "answer": "ocular"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who measures vision",
        "answer": "optometrist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "orthopedics",
        "answer": "treatment of skeletal deformities"
      },
      {
        "question": "orthodontia",
        "answer": "straightening of teeth"
      },
      {
        "question": "neuralgia",
        "answer": "nerve pain"
      },
      {
        "question": "neuritis",
        "answer": "inflammation of the nerves"
      },
      {
        "question": "geriatrics",
        "answer": "specialty dealing with medical problems of the elderly"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "cardiogram",
        "answer": "record of heart beats"
      },
      {
        "question": "cardiograph",
        "answer": "instrument for recording heartbeats"
      },
      {
        "question": "neurosis",
        "answer": "emotional disturbance"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychosis",
        "answer": "mental unbalance"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychiatry",
        "answer": "treatment of personality disorders"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "A gynecologist's patients are mostly men.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Ophtalmology is the study of eye diseases.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Orthopedics is the speialty dealing with the bones and jionts.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A cardiac patient has a heart ailment.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A person with a bad \"bite\" may profit from orthodontia.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Neuralgia is a disease of the bones.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A neurosis is the same as a psychosis.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Neuritis is inflammation of the nerves.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Psychiatry is a medical specialty that deals with mental, emotional, and personality disturbances.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A cardiograph is a device for recording heartbeats.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Psychiatric treatment is designed to relieve tensions, fears, and insecurities.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A doctor who specializes in pediatrics has very old patients.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A geriatrician has very young patients.",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "specialist who straightens teeth",
        "answer": "orthodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "nerve pain",
        "answer": "neuralgia"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical specialty dealing with bones and joints",
        "answer": "orthopedics"
      },
      {
        "question": "medical specialty dealing with emotional disturbances and mental illness",
        "answer": "psychiatry"
      },
      {
        "question": "inflammation of the nerves",
        "answer": "neuritis"
      },
      {
        "question": "emotional or personality disorder",
        "answer": "neurosis"
      },
      {
        "question": "mentally unbalanced",
        "answer": "psychotic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the heart",
        "answer": "cardiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "specialty dealing with medical problems of the elderly",
        "answer": "geriatrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "instrument that records heart action",
        "answer": "cardiograph"
      },
      {
        "question": "record produced by such an instrument",
        "answer": "cardiogram"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Mcq",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Specialist in female ailments",
        "answer": "gynecologist",
        "options": [
          "obstetrician",
          "gynecologist",
          "dermatologist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Specialist in children's diseases",
        "answer": "pediatrician",
        "options": [
          "orthopedist",
          "pediatrician",
          "internist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Specialist in eye diseases",
        "answer": "ophthalmologist",
        "options": [
          "cardiologist",
          "ophthalmologist",
          "optician"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Specialist in emotional disorders",
        "answer": "psychiatrist",
        "options": [
          "neurologist",
          "demagogue",
          "psychiatrist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Pertaining to medical treatment of elderly",
        "answer": "geriatric",
        "options": [
          "neurological",
          "obstetric",
          "geriatric"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Straightening of teeth",
        "answer": "orthodontia",
        "options": [
          "orthodontia",
          "orthopedic",
          "optometry"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Personality disorder",
        "answer": "neurosis",
        "options": [
          "neuritis",
          "neuralgia",
          "neurosis"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Mentally unbalanced",
        "answer": "psychotic",
        "options": [
          "neurotic",
          "psychotic",
          "cardiac"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Principles of teaching",
        "answer": "pedagogy",
        "options": [
          "demagoguery",
          "pedagogy",
          "psychosis"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "internus",
        "answer": "inside",
        "example": "internist"
      },
      {
        "question": "paidos (ped-)",
        "answer": "child",
        "example": "pediatrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedis",
        "answer": "foot",
        "example": "pedestrian"
      },
      {
        "question": "agogos",
        "answer": "leading",
        "example": "pedagogue"
      },
      {
        "question": "demos",
        "answer": "people",
        "example": "demagogue"
      },
      {
        "question": "derma",
        "answer": "skin",
        "example": "dermatologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "hypos",
        "answer": "under",
        "example": "hypodermic"
      },
      {
        "question": "ophthalmos",
        "answer": "eye",
        "example": "ophthalmologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "oculus",
        "answer": "eye",
        "example": "monocle"
      },
      {
        "question": "opsis, optikos",
        "answer": "view, vision, sight",
        "example": "optician"
      },
      {
        "question": "metron",
        "answer": "measurement",
        "example": "optometrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "orthos",
        "answer": "straight, correct",
        "example": "orthopedist"
      },
      {
        "question": "odontos",
        "answer": "tooth",
        "example": "orthodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "kardia",
        "answer": "heart",
        "example": "cardiologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "logos",
        "answer": "science, study",
        "example": "anthropologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "neuron",
        "answer": "nerve",
        "example": "neurologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "algos",
        "answer": "pain",
        "example": "neuralgia"
      },
      {
        "question": "psyche",
        "answer": "mind",
        "example": "psychiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "iateria",
        "answer": "medical healing",
        "example": "psychiatry"
      },
      {
        "question": "gera",
        "answer": "old age",
        "example": "geriatrics"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "psychologist",
        "answer": "behaviour"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychoanalyst",
        "answer": "\"the unconscious\""
      },
      {
        "question": "orthodontist",
        "answer": "teeth"
      },
      {
        "question": "optometrist",
        "answer": "vision"
      },
      {
        "question": "optician",
        "answer": "lenses and optical instruments"
      },
      {
        "question": "osteopath",
        "answer": "bones and blood vessles"
      },
      {
        "question": "chiropractor",
        "answer": "joints of the spine"
      },
      {
        "question": "podiatrist",
        "answer": "feet"
      },
      {
        "question": "graphologist",
        "answer": "handwriting"
      },
      {
        "question": "gerontologist",
        "answer": "problems of aging"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "A psychologist must also be a physician.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A pshychoanalyst follows Freudian techniques.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An orthodontist speializes in straightening teeth.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An optometrist prescribes and fits glasses.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An optician may prescribe glasses.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "An osteopath may use massage and other manipulative techniques.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A chiropractor has a medical degree.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A podiatrist may perform major surgery.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A graphologist analyzes characters from handwriting.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A gerontologist is interested in the non-medical problems of adolescence.",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "delves into unconscious",
        "answer": "psychoanalyst"
      },
      {
        "question": "uses either massage and manipulation or other standard medical procedures to treat illness",
        "answer": "osteopath"
      },
      {
        "question": "takes care of minor ailments of the feet",
        "answer": "podiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "straightens teeth",
        "answer": "orthodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "analyzes handwriting",
        "answer": "graphologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "grinds lenses and sells optical goods",
        "answer": "optician"
      },
      {
        "question": "deals with the non-medical problems of aging",
        "answer": "gerontologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "manipulates articulations connected to the spinal column",
        "answer": "chiropractor"
      },
      {
        "question": "studies and explains human behaviour",
        "answer": "psychologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "measures vision and prescribes glasses",
        "answer": "optometrist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "A psychologist must also be a physician.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A pshychoanalyst follows Freudian techniques.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An orthodontist speializes in straightening teeth.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An optometrist prescribes and fits glasses.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An optician may prescribe glasses.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "An osteopath may use massage and other manipulative techniques.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A chiropractor has a medical degree.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A podiatrist may perform major surgery.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A graphologist analyzes characters from handwriting.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A gerontologist is interested in the non-medical problems of adolescence.",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "delves into unconscious",
        "answer": "psychoanalyst"
      },
      {
        "question": "uses either massage and manipulation or other standard medical procedures to treat illness",
        "answer": "osteopath"
      },
      {
        "question": "takes care of minor ailments of the feet",
        "answer": "podiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "straightens teeth",
        "answer": "orthodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "analyzes handwriting",
        "answer": "graphologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "grinds lenses and sells optical goods",
        "answer": "optician"
      },
      {
        "question": "deals with the non-medical problems of aging",
        "answer": "gerontologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "manipulates articulations connected to the spinal column",
        "answer": "chiropractor"
      },
      {
        "question": "studies and explains human behaviour",
        "answer": "psychologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "measures vision and prescribes glasses",
        "answer": "optometrist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "psychology",
        "answer": "study of the human mind and behaviour"
      },
      {
        "question": "psyche",
        "answer": "one's inner or mental life, or self-image"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychic",
        "answer": "pertaining to the mind; extrasensory"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychopathy",
        "answer": "mental or emotional disturbance"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychosomatic",
        "answer": "describing the interaction of mind and body"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychoanalysis",
        "answer": "psychological treatment based on Freudian techniques"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychogenic",
        "answer": "originating in the mind or emotions"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychotherapy",
        "answer": "general term for psychological treatment"
      },
      {
        "question": "psychopath",
        "answer": "person lacking in social conscience or inner censor"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Psychological tretment aims at sharpening the intellect.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Psychic phenomena can be explained on rational or physical grounds",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Psychopathic personalities are normal and healthy.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A psychosomatic symptom is caused by organic disease.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Every therapist uses psychoanalysis.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A psychogenic illness originates in the mind or emotions.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A psychotherapist must have a medical degree.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Psychoanalytically oriented therapy uses Freudian techniques.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A psychopath is often a criminal.",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "one's inner or mental life, or self-image",
        "answer": "psyche"
      },
      {
        "question": "the adjective that denotes the interactions, especially in illness, between mind and body",
        "answer": "psychosomatic"
      },
      {
        "question": "mentally or emotionally disturbed",
        "answer": "psyschopathic"
      },
      {
        "question": "study of behaviour",
        "answer": "psychology"
      },
      {
        "question": "extrasensory",
        "answer": "psychic"
      },
      {
        "question": "treatment by Freudian techniques",
        "answer": "psychoanalysis"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the study of behaviour",
        "answer": "psychological"
      },
      {
        "question": "of mental or emotional origin",
        "answer": "psychogenic"
      },
      {
        "question": "general term for treatment of emotional disorders",
        "answer": "psychotherapy"
      },
      {
        "question": "antisocial person",
        "answer": "psychopath"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "orthodontia",
        "answer": "specialty of tooth straightening"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedodontia",
        "answer": "specialty of child dentistry"
      },
      {
        "question": "periodontia",
        "answer": "specialty of the gums"
      },
      {
        "question": "endodontia",
        "answer": "dental specialty involving the pulp and root canal"
      },
      {
        "question": "exodontia",
        "answer": "specialty of tooth extraction"
      },
      {
        "question": "barometer",
        "answer": "instrument that measures atmospheric pressure"
      },
      {
        "question": "sphygmomanometer",
        "answer": "blood-pressure apparatus"
      },
      {
        "question": "osteopathy",
        "answer": "specialty arising from the theory that pressure of the bones on nerves and blood vessles may cause disease"
      },
      {
        "question": "podiatry",
        "answer": "treatment of minor ailments of the foot"
      },
      {
        "question": "thermometer",
        "answer": "instrument to measure heat"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "octopus",
        "answer": "eight-armed sea creature"
      },
      {
        "question": "platypus",
        "answer": "egg-laying mammal with webbed feet"
      },
      {
        "question": "podium",
        "answer": "speaker's platform"
      },
      {
        "question": "chiropody",
        "answer": "treatment of minor ailments of the foot"
      },
      {
        "question": "chiropractic",
        "answer": "maintenance of integrity of the nervous system by manipulation and message"
      },
      {
        "question": "chirography",
        "answer": "handwriting"
      },
      {
        "question": "chiromancy",
        "answer": "palm reading"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Orthodontia is a branch of dentistry.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Doctors use sphygmomanometers to check blood pressure.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Osteopathic physicians may use standard medical procedures.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Chiropractic deals with handwriting.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Chiropody and podiatry are synonymous terms.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A podium is a place from which a lecture might be delivered.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A pedodontist is a foot doctor.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A periodontist is a gum specialist.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An endodontist does root-canal therapy.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "An exodontist extracts teeth.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A barometer measures heat.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "An octopus has eight arms.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A platypus is a land animal.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A tripod has four legs.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A chirographer is an expert at penmanship.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A chiromancer reads palms.",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pertaining to child dentistry (adj.)",
        "answer": "pedodontic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to treatment of the foot (adj.)",
        "answer": "podiatric"
      },
      {
        "question": "blood-preasure apparatus",
        "answer": "sphygmomanometer"
      },
      {
        "question": "three-legged stand",
        "answer": "tripod"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the treatment of diseases by manipulation to relieve pressure of the bones on nerves and blood vessels (adj.)",
        "answer": "osteopathic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to handwriting (adj.)",
        "answer": "chirographic"
      },
      {
        "question": "gum specialist",
        "answer": "periodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "tretment of ailments of the foot",
        "answer": "podiatry or chiropody"
      },
      {
        "question": "stand for a speaker",
        "answer": "podium"
      },
      {
        "question": "dentist specializing in treating the pulp of the tooth or in doing root-canal therapy",
        "answer": "endodontist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the specialty of tooth extraction (adj.)",
        "answer": "exodontic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaiing to the measurement of atmospheric pressure (adj.)",
        "answer": "barometric"
      },
      {
        "question": "palm reading (noun)",
        "answer": "chiromancy"
      },
      {
        "question": "handwriting",
        "answer": "chirography"
      },
      {
        "question": "the practice of manipulating bodily articulations to relieve ailments",
        "answer": "chiropractic"
      },
      {
        "question": "egg-laying mammal",
        "answer": "platypus"
      },
      {
        "question": "eight-armed sea creature",
        "answer": "octopus"
      },
      {
        "question": "instrument to measure heat",
        "answer": "thermometer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "graphology",
        "answer": "analysis of handwriting"
      },
      {
        "question": "calligraphy",
        "answer": "beautiful handwriting; handwriting as an artistic expression"
      },
      {
        "question": "callipygian",
        "answer": "possessed of beautiful buttocks"
      },
      {
        "question": "cacography",
        "answer": "ugly, bad, illegible handwriting"
      },
      {
        "question": "gerontology",
        "answer": "science of the social, economic, etc. problems of the aged"
      },
      {
        "question": "senility",
        "answer": "deteriorated old age"
      },
      {
        "question": "senescence",
        "answer": "condition of aging or growing old"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Graphology analyzes the grammar, spelling and sentence structure of written material.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A calligrapher creates artistic forms out of alphabetical symbols.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Tight slacks are best worn by those of callipygian anatomy.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Cacographic writing is easy to read.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Gerontology aims to help old people live more comfortably.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Senile people are old but still vigorous and mentally alert.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "In a society dedicated to the worship of youth, senescence is not an attractive prospect.",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the study of the non-medical problems of the aged (adj.)",
        "answer": "gerontological"
      },
      {
        "question": "growing old (adj.)",
        "answer": "senescent"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to handwriting as an artistic expression (adj.)",
        "answer": "calligraphic"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who uses ugly, illegible handwriting",
        "answer": "cacographer"
      },
      {
        "question": "mentally and physically deteriorated from old age",
        "answer": "senile"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the analysis of handwriting (adj.)",
        "answer": "graphological"
      },
      {
        "question": "possessed of beautiful or shapely buttocks",
        "answer": "callipygian"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Mcq",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Practitioner trained in Freudian techniques",
        "answer": "psychoanalyst",
        "options": [
          "psychologist",
          "psychoanalyst",
          "psychotherapist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Foot doctor",
        "answer": "podiatrist",
        "options": [
          "podiatrist",
          "osteopath",
          "chiropractor"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Handwriting analyst",
        "answer": "graphologist",
        "options": [
          "graphologist",
          "chirographer",
          "cacographer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Mentally or emotionally disturbed",
        "answer": "psychopathic",
        "options": [
          "psychological",
          "psychopathic",
          "psychic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Originating in the emotions",
        "answer": "psychogenic",
        "options": [
          "psychic",
          "psychogenic",
          "psychoanalytic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Describing bodily ailments tied up with the emotions",
        "answer": "psychosomatic",
        "options": [
          "psychosomatic",
          "psychopathic",
          "psychiatric"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Gum specialist",
        "answer": "periodontist",
        "options": [
          "periodontist",
          "pedodontist",
          "endodontist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Specialist in tooth extraction",
        "answer": "exodontist",
        "options": [
          "orthodontist",
          "exodontist",
          "endodontist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Blood-pressure apparatus",
        "answer": "sphygmomanometer",
        "options": [
          "barometer",
          "thermometer",
          "sphygmomanometer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Prediction by palm reading",
        "answer": "chiromancy",
        "options": [
          "chirography",
          "chiropody",
          "chiromancy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Possessed of a shapely posterior",
        "answer": "callipygiian",
        "options": [
          "calligraphic",
          "callipygiian",
          "adolescent"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Artistic handwriting",
        "answer": "calligraphy",
        "options": [
          "calligraphy",
          "chirography",
          "graphology"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Growing old",
        "answer": "senescent",
        "options": [
          "senile",
          "geriatric",
          "senescent"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Medical specialty dealing with the aged",
        "answer": "chiropractic",
        "options": [
          "gerontology",
          "geriatrics",
          "chiropractic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Antisocial person who may commit criminal acts",
        "answer": "psychopath",
        "options": [
          "psychopath",
          "sociopath",
          "osteopath"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "psyche",
        "answer": "mind",
        "example": "psychiatry"
      },
      {
        "question": "iateria",
        "answer": "medical healing",
        "example": "podiatry"
      },
      {
        "question": "soma",
        "answer": "body",
        "example": "psychosomatic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "disease",
        "example": "osteopath"
      },
      {
        "question": "orthos",
        "answer": "straight, correct",
        "example": "orthodontia"
      },
      {
        "question": "paidos (ped-)",
        "answer": "child",
        "example": "pedodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "odontos",
        "answer": "tooth",
        "example": "exodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "pous, podos",
        "answer": "foot",
        "example": "platypus"
      },
      {
        "question": "cheir (chiro-)",
        "answer": "hand",
        "example": "chiropodist"
      },
      {
        "question": "okto",
        "answer": "eight",
        "example": "octopus"
      },
      {
        "question": "graphein",
        "answer": "to write",
        "example": "graphology"
      },
      {
        "question": "kallos",
        "answer": "beauty",
        "example": "calligraphy"
      },
      {
        "question": "pyge",
        "answer": "buttocks",
        "example": "callipygian"
      },
      {
        "question": "kakos",
        "answer": "bad, ugly",
        "example": "cacography"
      },
      {
        "question": "photos",
        "answer": "light",
        "example": "photography"
      },
      {
        "question": "tele-",
        "answer": "distance",
        "example": "telegraph"
      },
      {
        "question": "bios",
        "answer": "life",
        "example": "biography"
      },
      {
        "question": "geras",
        "answer": "old age",
        "example": "geriatrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "geron",
        "answer": "old man",
        "example": "gerontology"
      },
      {
        "question": "senex",
        "answer": "old",
        "example": "senate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "anthropologist",
        "answer": "development of the human race"
      },
      {
        "question": "astronomer",
        "answer": "celestial phenomena"
      },
      {
        "question": "geologist",
        "answer": "the earth"
      },
      {
        "question": "biologist",
        "answer": "all forms of living matter"
      },
      {
        "question": "botanist",
        "answer": "plant life"
      },
      {
        "question": "zoologist",
        "answer": "animal life"
      },
      {
        "question": "entomologist",
        "answer": "insect forms"
      },
      {
        "question": "philologist",
        "answer": "language"
      },
      {
        "question": "semanticist",
        "answer": "meanings and psychological effects of words"
      },
      {
        "question": "sociologist",
        "answer": "community and family life"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "insects",
        "answer": "entomologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "language",
        "answer": "philologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "social conditions",
        "answer": "sociologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "history of development of mankind",
        "answer": "anthropologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "meanings of words",
        "answer": "semanticist"
      },
      {
        "question": "plants",
        "answer": "botanist"
      },
      {
        "question": "the earth",
        "answer": "geologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "the heavenly bodies",
        "answer": "astronomer"
      },
      {
        "question": "all living things",
        "answer": "biologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "animals",
        "answer": "zoologist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "anthropology",
        "answer": "science of human development"
      },
      {
        "question": "astronomy",
        "answer": "science of the heavens"
      },
      {
        "question": "astrology",
        "answer": "theory of the influence of planets and stars on human events"
      },
      {
        "question": "geology",
        "answer": "science of the composition of the earth"
      },
      {
        "question": "biology",
        "answer": "science of all living matter"
      },
      {
        "question": "geometry",
        "answer": "mathematical science of figures, shapes etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "botany",
        "answer": "science of plants"
      },
      {
        "question": "zoology",
        "answer": "science of animal life"
      },
      {
        "question": "geography",
        "answer": "science of earth mapping"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "autopsy",
        "answer": "dissection and examination of a corpse to determine the cause of death"
      },
      {
        "question": "biopsy",
        "answer": "examination of living tissue"
      },
      {
        "question": "biography",
        "answer": "story of one's own life"
      },
      {
        "question": "autobiography",
        "answer": "story of someone's life"
      },
      {
        "question": "zodiac",
        "answer": "diagram of path of sun, moon, and planets"
      },
      {
        "question": "astronaut",
        "answer": "\"sailor among the stars\""
      },
      {
        "question": "cosmonaut",
        "answer": "\"sailor of the universe\""
      },
      {
        "question": "aster",
        "answer": "star-shaped flower"
      },
      {
        "question": "disaster",
        "answer": "great misfortune"
      },
      {
        "question": "autonomy",
        "answer": "self-rule"
      },
      {
        "question": "metronome",
        "answer": "instrument to measure musical time"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Are anthropological studies concerned with plant life?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are astronomical numbers extremely small?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an astrologer interested in the time and date of your birth?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Are nautical maneuvers carried on at sea?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a disastrous earthquake take a huge toll of life and property?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do geological investigations sometimes determine where oil is to be found?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a geometrician work with mathematics?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do geographical shifts in population sometimes affect the economy of an area?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a biographical novel deal with life of a real person?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is botany a biological science?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the United States politically autonomous?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a biopsy performed on a dead body?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a metronome used in the study of mathematics?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an autopsy performed to correct a surgical problem?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an author write an autobiography about someone else's life?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the science of animals (adj.)",
        "answer": "zoological"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the science of plants (adj.)",
        "answer": "botanical"
      },
      {
        "question": "dissection of a corpse to determine the cause of death",
        "answer": "autopsy"
      },
      {
        "question": "story of one's life, self-written",
        "answer": "autobiography"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the science of all living matter (adj.)",
        "answer": "biological"
      },
      {
        "question": "science of the measurement of figures",
        "answer": "geometry"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the science of the earth's composition (adj.)",
        "answer": "geological"
      },
      {
        "question": "branch of physics dealing with the composition of celestial bodies",
        "answer": "astrophysics"
      },
      {
        "question": "star-shaped flower",
        "answer": "aster"
      },
      {
        "question": "very high in number; pertaining to the science of the heavens (adj.)",
        "answer": "astronomical"
      },
      {
        "question": "science of heavenly bodies",
        "answer": "astronomy"
      },
      {
        "question": "science of the development of mankind",
        "answer": "anthropology"
      },
      {
        "question": "person who believes human events are influenced by the paths of the sun, moon, and planets",
        "answer": "astrologer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "microscopic examiniation of living tissue",
        "answer": "biopsy"
      },
      {
        "question": "self-government",
        "answer": "autonomy"
      },
      {
        "question": "time measurer for music",
        "answer": "metronome"
      },
      {
        "question": "voyager among the stars",
        "answer": "astronaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "traveler through the universe",
        "answer": "cosmonaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "great misfortune",
        "answer": "disaster"
      },
      {
        "question": "mapping of the earth (noun)",
        "answer": "geography"
      },
      {
        "question": "self-government (adj.)",
        "answer": "autonomous"
      },
      {
        "question": "diagram used in astrology",
        "answer": "zodiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to such a diagram (adj.)",
        "answer": "zodiacal"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to ships, sailing, etc.",
        "answer": "nautical"
      },
      {
        "question": "star-shaped symbol",
        "answer": "asterisk"
      },
      {
        "question": "story of a person's life",
        "answer": "biography"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "entomology",
        "answer": "science dealing with insects"
      },
      {
        "question": "eccentricity",
        "answer": "strangeness; oddness; unconventionality"
      },
      {
        "question": "anatomy",
        "answer": "physical structure"
      },
      {
        "question": "dichotomy",
        "answer": "condition or state of being split into two parts"
      },
      {
        "question": "epitome",
        "answer": "summary; representation of the whole"
      },
      {
        "question": "philology",
        "answer": "linguistics"
      },
      {
        "question": "semantics",
        "answer": "science of the meanings and effects of words"
      },
      {
        "question": "sociology",
        "answer": "science of social structures and customs"
      },
      {
        "question": "aphrodisiac",
        "answer": "that which causes sexual arousal"
      },
      {
        "question": "philanthropy",
        "answer": "charitable works"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "dichotomize",
        "answer": "to split in two"
      },
      {
        "question": "epitomize",
        "answer": "to summarize"
      },
      {
        "question": "philander",
        "answer": "to engage in extramarital sex"
      },
      {
        "question": "philter",
        "answer": "love potion; aphrodisiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "bibliophile",
        "answer": "book collector"
      },
      {
        "question": "anglophile",
        "answer": "one fond of British people, customs, etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "asocial",
        "answer": "withdrawn from contact with people"
      },
      {
        "question": "tome",
        "answer": "dull, heavy book"
      },
      {
        "question": "philological",
        "answer": "pertaining to the study of language"
      },
      {
        "question": "sociological",
        "answer": "pertaining to the science of group cultures, conventions, etc."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Is a philanderer likely to be faithful to a spouse?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Did Dr. Jekyll-Mr. Hyde lead a dichotomous existence?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an egoist the epitome of selfishness?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a philanthropist antisocial?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an aphrodisiac intended to reduce sexual interest?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a bibliophile's cheif aim the enjoyment of literature?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a philologist understand etymology?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a semanticist interested in more than the dictionary meanings of words?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an asocial person interested in improving social conditions?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a light novel considered a tome?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the study of social customs (adj.)",
        "answer": "sociological"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the psychological effects of words (adj.)",
        "answer": "semantic"
      },
      {
        "question": "lover and collector of books",
        "answer": "bibliophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "make love promiscuously",
        "answer": "philander"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the science of linguistics (adj.)",
        "answer": "philological"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the study of insects (adj.)",
        "answer": "entomological"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who admires British customs",
        "answer": "anglophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "smallest particle, so-called",
        "answer": "atom"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to the structure of a body (adj.)",
        "answer": "anatomical"
      },
      {
        "question": "a dull, heavy book",
        "answer": "tome"
      },
      {
        "question": "split in two (adj.)",
        "answer": "dichotomous"
      },
      {
        "question": "to split in two",
        "answer": "dichotomize"
      },
      {
        "question": "a condensation, summary, or representation of the whole",
        "answer": "epitome"
      },
      {
        "question": "to stand for the whole; to summarize",
        "answer": "epitomize"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to charitable activities (adj.)",
        "answer": "philanthropic"
      },
      {
        "question": "out of the norm; odd",
        "answer": "eccentric"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who \"plays around\"",
        "answer": "philanderer"
      },
      {
        "question": "arousing sexual desire (adj.)",
        "answer": "aphrodisiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "science of the manner in which groups function",
        "answer": "sociology"
      },
      {
        "question": "self-isolated from contact with people",
        "answer": "asocial"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Mcq",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Student of the stars and other heavenly phenomena",
        "answer": "astronomer",
        "options": [
          "geologist",
          "astronomer",
          "anthropologist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Student of plant life",
        "answer": "botanist",
        "options": [
          "botanist",
          "zoologist",
          "biologist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Student of insect life",
        "answer": "entomologist",
        "options": [
          "sociologist",
          "entomologist",
          "etymologist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Student of the meaning and psychology of words",
        "answer": "semanticist",
        "options": [
          "philologist",
          "semanticist",
          "etymologist"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Analysis of living tissue",
        "answer": "biopsy",
        "options": [
          "autopsy",
          "biopsy",
          "autonomy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "That which arouses sexual desire",
        "answer": "aphrodisiac",
        "options": [
          "zodiac",
          "bibliophile",
          "aphrodisiac"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Self-governing",
        "answer": "autonomous",
        "options": [
          "autobiographical",
          "autonomous",
          "dichotomous"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Part that represents the whole",
        "answer": "epitome",
        "options": [
          "epitome",
          "dichotomy",
          "metronome"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "One who physically travels in space",
        "answer": "astronaut",
        "options": [
          "astronomer",
          "astrologer",
          "astronaut"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "One who has extramarital affairs",
        "answer": "philanderer",
        "options": [
          "cosmonaut",
          "philanderer",
          "philanthropist"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "anthropos",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "example": "anthropology"
      },
      {
        "question": "logos",
        "answer": "word, speech",
        "example": "philology"
      },
      {
        "question": "astron",
        "answer": "star",
        "example": "astronomy"
      },
      {
        "question": "nautes",
        "answer": "sailor",
        "example": "astronaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "nomos",
        "answer": "law, order, arrangement",
        "example": "metronome"
      },
      {
        "question": "autos",
        "answer": "self",
        "example": "autonomy"
      },
      {
        "question": "ge (geo-)",
        "answer": "earth",
        "example": "geology"
      },
      {
        "question": "graphein",
        "answer": "to write",
        "example": "biography"
      },
      {
        "question": "opsis, optikos",
        "answer": "view, vision",
        "example": "autopsy"
      },
      {
        "question": "zoion",
        "answer": "animal",
        "example": "zodiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "tome",
        "answer": "a cutting",
        "example": "entomology"
      },
      {
        "question": "sectus",
        "answer": "cut",
        "example": "insect"
      },
      {
        "question": "lingua",
        "answer": "tongue",
        "example": "linguistics"
      },
      {
        "question": "philein",
        "answer": "to love",
        "example": "philanthropy"
      },
      {
        "question": "sophos",
        "answer": "wise",
        "example": "philosophy"
      },
      {
        "question": "biblion",
        "answer": "book",
        "example": "bibliophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "anglus",
        "answer": "English",
        "example": "anglophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "socius",
        "answer": "companion",
        "example": "sociology"
      },
      {
        "question": "logos",
        "answer": "science, study",
        "example": "biology"
      },
      {
        "question": "bios",
        "answer": "life",
        "example": "biopsy"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "notorious",
        "answer": "unfavorable known"
      },
      {
        "question": "consummate",
        "answer": "finished, perfect, artistic"
      },
      {
        "question": "incorrigible",
        "answer": "beyond reform"
      },
      {
        "question": "inveterate",
        "answer": "from long-standing habit"
      },
      {
        "question": "congenital",
        "answer": "from birth"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronic",
        "answer": "continuing over a long period of time; recurring"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathological",
        "answer": "diseased"
      },
      {
        "question": "unconscionable",
        "answer": "without conscience or scruples"
      },
      {
        "question": "glib",
        "answer": "suspiciously smooth"
      },
      {
        "question": "egregious",
        "answer": "outstandingly bad or vicious"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Do people become notorious for good acts?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is Beethoven considered a consummate musical genius?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "If a criminal is truly incorrigible, is there any point in attempting rehabilitation?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an inverterate smoker smoke only occasionally?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a congenital deformity one that occurs late in life?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a chronic invalid ill much of the time?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a pathological condition normal and healthy?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "If a person commits an unconscionable act of cruelty, is there any regret, remorse, or guilt?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a glib talker awkward and hesitant in speech?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an egregious error very bad?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "outstandingly vicious; so bad as to be in a class by itelf",
        "answer": "egregious"
      },
      {
        "question": "starting at birth",
        "answer": "congenital"
      },
      {
        "question": "happening over and over again; continuing for a long time",
        "answer": "chronic"
      },
      {
        "question": "widely and unfavorably known (as for antisocial acts, character weaknesses, immoral or unethical behaviour, etc.)",
        "answer": "notorious"
      },
      {
        "question": "beyond correction",
        "answer": "incorrigible"
      },
      {
        "question": "smooth and persuasive; unusually, almost suspiciously, fluent",
        "answer": "glib"
      },
      {
        "question": "long addicted to a habit",
        "answer": "inveterate"
      },
      {
        "question": "perfect in the practice of an art; extremely skillful",
        "answer": "consummate"
      },
      {
        "question": "unscrupulous; entirely without conscience",
        "answer": "unconscionable"
      },
      {
        "question": "diseased",
        "answer": "pathological"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "FillInTheBlank",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "This person has gambled, day in and day out, for as long as anyone can remember gambling has become a deep-rooted habit.",
        "answer": "inveterate",
        "blank": "An _ gambler"
      },
      {
        "question": "Born with a clubfoot",
        "answer": "congenital",
        "blank": "A _ deformity"
      },
      {
        "question": "Someone known the world over for criminal acts",
        "answer": "notorious",
        "blank": "A _ criminal"
      },
      {
        "question": "An invading army kills, maims, and tortures without mercy, compunction, or regret.",
        "answer": "unconscionable",
        "blank": "A _ acts of cruelty"
      },
      {
        "question": "The suspect answers the detective's questions easily, fluently, almost too smoothly.",
        "answer": "glib",
        "blank": "_ responses"
      },
      {
        "question": "A person reaches the acme of perfection as an actress or actor.",
        "answer": "consummate",
        "blank": "A _ performer"
      },
      {
        "question": "No one can change someone's absurdly romantic attitude toward life.",
        "answer": "incorrigible",
        "blank": "An _ romantic"
      },
      {
        "question": "A mistake so bad that it defies description",
        "answer": "egregious",
        "blank": "An _ blunder"
      },
      {
        "question": "Drunk almost all the time, again and again and again-periods of sobriety are few and ver, very far between",
        "answer": "chronic",
        "blank": "A _ alchoholic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Doctors find a persistent, dangerous infection in the bladder",
        "answer": "pathological",
        "blank": "A _ condition"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "notoriety",
        "answer": "ill fame"
      },
      {
        "question": "to consummate (v.)",
        "answer": "bring to completion; top off"
      },
      {
        "question": "consummacy",
        "answer": "state of artistic height"
      },
      {
        "question": "incorrigibility",
        "answer": "state of being beyond reform or correction"
      },
      {
        "question": "inverteracy",
        "answer": "state of being long established in a habit"
      },
      {
        "question": "genetics",
        "answer": "science of heredity"
      },
      {
        "question": "genealogy",
        "answer": "study of ancestry"
      },
      {
        "question": "genital",
        "answer": "referring to reproduction, or to the reproductive or sexual organs"
      },
      {
        "question": "genesis",
        "answer": "beginning, origin"
      },
      {
        "question": "hereditary",
        "answer": "referring to characteristics passed on to offspring by parents"
      },
      {
        "question": "gene",
        "answer": "particle that transmits hereditary characteristics"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Does notoriety usually comes to prepetrators of mass murders?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the product of a consummately skillful counterfeiter likely to be taken as genuine?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is incorrigibility in a criminal a sign that rehabilitation is possible?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a geneticist interested in your parents' characteristics?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does inveteracy suggest that a habit is new?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "When you consummate a deal, do you back out of it?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a veteran actress long experienced at her art?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do genes determine heredity?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a geanologist interested in your family origins?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Are the genital organs used in reproduction?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the genesis of something the final point?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are hereditary characteristics derived from parents?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "sexual; reproductive",
        "answer": "genital"
      },
      {
        "question": "to complete",
        "answer": "consummate"
      },
      {
        "question": "wide and unfavorable reputation",
        "answer": "notoriety"
      },
      {
        "question": "particle in the chromosome of a cell that transmits a characteristics from parent to offspring",
        "answer": "gene"
      },
      {
        "question": "completion",
        "answer": "consummation"
      },
      {
        "question": "inability to be reformed",
        "answer": "incorrigibility"
      },
      {
        "question": "the science that deals with the transmission of characteristics from parents to children",
        "answer": "genetics"
      },
      {
        "question": "referring to a quality or characteristic that is inherited (adj.)",
        "answer": "hereditary"
      },
      {
        "question": "beginning or origin",
        "answer": "genesis"
      },
      {
        "question": "student of family roots or origins",
        "answer": "geanologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "height of skill or artistry",
        "answer": "consummacy"
      },
      {
        "question": "transmitted by heredity",
        "answer": "genetic"
      },
      {
        "question": "quality of a habit that has been established over many years",
        "answer": "inveteracy"
      },
      {
        "question": "a person long experienced at a profession, art, or business",
        "answer": "veteran"
      },
      {
        "question": "pertaining to a study of family origins (adj.)",
        "answer": "geanological"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "chronicity",
        "answer": "condition of continual or repeated recurrence"
      },
      {
        "question": "anachronism",
        "answer": "something, or someone, out of time"
      },
      {
        "question": "incongruity",
        "answer": "something, or state of being, out of place"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronology",
        "answer": "calendar of events in order of occurrence"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronometer",
        "answer": "timepiece; device that measures time very accurately"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronometry",
        "answer": "measurement of time"
      },
      {
        "question": "synchronization",
        "answer": "act of occurring, or of causing to occur, at the same time"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathology",
        "answer": "disease; study of disease"
      },
      {
        "question": "sympathy",
        "answer": "a sharing or understanding of another's feeling"
      },
      {
        "question": "telepathy",
        "answer": "ESP; communication from a distance"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "pathologist",
        "answer": "one who examines tissue to diagnose disease"
      },
      {
        "question": "antipathy",
        "answer": "hostility; strong dislike"
      },
      {
        "question": "apathy",
        "answer": "lack of feeling; non-responsiveness"
      },
      {
        "question": "empathy ",
        "answer": "identification with another's feelings"
      },
      {
        "question": "synchronize",
        "answer": "happen, or cause to happen, at the same time or rate"
      },
      {
        "question": "empathize",
        "answer": "share another's feelings so strongly as to experience those feelings oneself"
      },
      {
        "question": "anachronous",
        "answer": "out of time"
      },
      {
        "question": "incongruous",
        "answer": "out of place"
      },
      {
        "question": "synchronous",
        "answer": "occurring at the same time or rate"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathetic",
        "answer": "suffering; arousing sympathy or pity"
      },
      {
        "question": "telepathic",
        "answer": "relating to extrasensory perception"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Are these dates in chronological order? 1492, 1941, 1586",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is pathology the study of healthy tissues?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is telepathic communication carried on by telephone?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a sympathetic response show an understanding of another's feelings?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is one antipathetic to things, ideas, or people one finds agreeable?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Do apathetic people react strongly?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does an empathic response show indentification with the feelings of another?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is a swimsuit incongruous attire at a formal ceremony?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an anachronistic attitude up to date?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Are synchronous movements out of time with one another?",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "in order of time",
        "answer": "chronological"
      },
      {
        "question": "out of place",
        "answer": "incongruous"
      },
      {
        "question": "out of time",
        "answer": "anachronous"
      },
      {
        "question": "out of time",
        "answer": "anachronistic"
      },
      {
        "question": "something, or state of being, out of place",
        "answer": "incongruity"
      },
      {
        "question": "lack of feeling",
        "answer": "apathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "measurer of time",
        "answer": "chronometer"
      },
      {
        "question": "study of disease",
        "answer": "pathology"
      },
      {
        "question": "feeling of hostility or dislike",
        "answer": "antipathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "to occur, or cause to occur, at the same time or rate",
        "answer": "synchronize"
      },
      {
        "question": "evoking sorrow or pity",
        "answer": "pathetic"
      },
      {
        "question": "something out of time",
        "answer": "anachronism"
      },
      {
        "question": "state of recurring again and again",
        "answer": "chronicity"
      },
      {
        "question": "extrasensory perception",
        "answer": "telepathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "one who examines tissue to diagnose disease",
        "answer": "pathologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "identification with the feelings of another",
        "answer": "empathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "happening at the same time or rate (adj.)",
        "answer": "synchronous"
      },
      {
        "question": "skillful at thought transference without sensory communication",
        "answer": "telepathic"
      },
      {
        "question": "calendar of events in time sequence",
        "answer": "chronology"
      },
      {
        "question": "referring to the measurement of time (adj.)",
        "answer": "chronometric"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "unconscionability",
        "answer": "lack of conscience"
      },
      {
        "question": "omniscience",
        "answer": "infinite knowledge"
      },
      {
        "question": "prescience",
        "answer": "foreknowledge"
      },
      {
        "question": "nescience",
        "answer": "ignorance"
      },
      {
        "question": "glibness",
        "answer": "suspiciously smooth fluency"
      },
      {
        "question": "egregiousness",
        "answer": "outstanding badness or viciousness"
      },
      {
        "question": "gregariousness",
        "answer": "religious group; a massing together"
      },
      {
        "question": "congregation",
        "answer": "religious group; a massing together"
      },
      {
        "question": "segregation",
        "answer": "exclusion from the herd; a setting apart"
      },
      {
        "question": "aggregate (n.)",
        "answer": "total; mass; whole"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Is unconscionability one of the signs of the psychopath?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Can anyone be truly omniscient?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a prescient fear indicate some knowledge of the future?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is nescience a result of learning?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Does glibness make someone sound sincere and trustworthy?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is egregiousness an admirable quality?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Do gregarious people enjoy parties?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do spectators congregate at sports events?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do we often segregate hardened criminals from the rest of society?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Is an aggregation of problems a whole mass of problems?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "enjoying groups and companionship",
        "answer": "gregarious"
      },
      {
        "question": "ignorant",
        "answer": "nescient"
      },
      {
        "question": "state of not being held back from antisocial behaviour by one's conscience",
        "answer": "unconscionability"
      },
      {
        "question": "having knowledge of an event before it occurs (adj.)",
        "answer": "prescient"
      },
      {
        "question": "a religious \"flock\"",
        "answer": "congregation"
      },
      {
        "question": "a total, whole, or mass",
        "answer": "aggregate or aggregation"
      },
      {
        "question": "to separate from the rest",
        "answer": "segregate"
      },
      {
        "question": "suspiciously smooth fluency",
        "answer": "glibness"
      },
      {
        "question": "all-knowing (adj.)",
        "answer": "omniscient"
      },
      {
        "question": "to come together into a group or mass",
        "answer": "congregate"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Mcq",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Highly skilled",
        "answer": "consummate",
        "options": [
          "consummate",
          "inveterate",
          "notorious"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Beyond reform",
        "answer": "incorrigible",
        "options": [
          "inveterate",
          "incorrigible",
          "glib"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Dating from birth",
        "answer": "congenital",
        "options": [
          "inveterate",
          "congenital",
          "psychopathic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Outstandingly bad",
        "answer": "egregious",
        "options": [
          "egregious",
          "unconscionable",
          "chronic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Science of heredity",
        "answer": "genetics",
        "options": [
          "pathology",
          "genetics",
          "orthopedics"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Out of time",
        "answer": "anachronous",
        "options": [
          "incongruous",
          "anachronous",
          "synchronous"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Study of disease",
        "answer": "pathology",
        "options": [
          "pathology",
          "telepathy",
          "antipathy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Fond of company, friends, group activities, etc.",
        "answer": "gregarious",
        "options": [
          "apathetic",
          "gregarious",
          "chronological"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Indifferent",
        "answer": "apathetic",
        "options": [
          "antipathetic",
          "pathetic",
          "apathetic"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Long accustomed in habit",
        "answer": "inveterate",
        "options": [
          "incorrigible",
          "notorious",
          "inveterate"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Study of family ancestry",
        "answer": "geanology",
        "options": [
          "geanology",
          "genetics",
          "genesis"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "To complete, finish, top off",
        "answer": "consummate",
        "options": [
          "synchronize",
          "consummate",
          "empathize"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Accurate timepiece",
        "answer": "chronometer",
        "options": [
          "anachronism",
          "chronology",
          "chronometer"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Identification with the feelings of another",
        "answer": "empathy",
        "options": [
          "sympathy",
          "apathy",
          "empathy"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Thought transference; extrasensory perception",
        "answer": "telepathy",
        "options": [
          "telepathy",
          "empathy",
          "omniscience"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Ignorance",
        "answer": "nescience",
        "options": [
          "omniscience",
          "prescience",
          "nescience"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "To gather into a group",
        "answer": "congregate",
        "options": [
          "congregate",
          "segregate",
          "synchronize"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "notus",
        "answer": "known",
        "example": "notorious"
      },
      {
        "question": "summus",
        "answer": "highest",
        "example": "summit"
      },
      {
        "question": "corrigo",
        "answer": "to correct, set straight",
        "example": "incorrigible"
      },
      {
        "question": "vetus",
        "answer": "old",
        "example": "veteran"
      },
      {
        "question": "senex",
        "answer": "old",
        "example": "senile"
      },
      {
        "question": "genesis",
        "answer": "birth",
        "example": "congenital"
      },
      {
        "question": "logos",
        "answer": "science, study",
        "example": "genealogy"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronos",
        "answer": "time",
        "example": "chronic"
      },
      {
        "question": "metron",
        "answer": "measurement",
        "example": "chronometer"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "disease",
        "example": "pathology"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "suffering",
        "example": "pathetic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "feeling",
        "example": "empathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "grex, gregis",
        "answer": "herd, flock",
        "example": "gregarious"
      },
      {
        "question": "scio",
        "answer": "to know",
        "example": "unconscionable"
      },
      {
        "question": "sciens",
        "answer": "knowing",
        "example": "prescience"
      },
      {
        "question": "omnis",
        "answer": "all",
        "example": "omniscient"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "ego",
        "answer": "I, self",
        "example": "egoism"
      },
      {
        "question": "misein",
        "answer": "to hate",
        "example": "misanthrope"
      },
      {
        "question": "gamos",
        "answer": "marriage",
        "example": "bigamy"
      },
      {
        "question": "gyne",
        "answer": "woman",
        "example": "gynecology"
      },
      {
        "question": "derma",
        "answer": "skin",
        "example": "dermatologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "orthos",
        "answer": "straight, correct",
        "example": "orthodontia"
      },
      {
        "question": "psyche",
        "answer": "mind, soul, spirit",
        "example": "psychotic"
      },
      {
        "question": "neuron",
        "answer": "nerve",
        "example": "neurology"
      },
      {
        "question": "logos",
        "answer": "science, study",
        "example": "biology"
      },
      {
        "question": "bios",
        "answer": "life",
        "example": "biopsy"
      },
      {
        "question": "opsis, optikos",
        "answer": "view, sight, vision",
        "example": "autopsy, optical"
      },
      {
        "question": "algos",
        "answer": "pain",
        "example": "neuralgia"
      },
      {
        "question": "agogos",
        "answer": "leading",
        "example": "demagogue"
      },
      {
        "question": "pedis",
        "answer": "foot",
        "example": "pedestrian"
      },
      {
        "question": "paidos (ped-)",
        "answer": "child",
        "example": "pediatrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "demos",
        "answer": "people",
        "example": "democracy"
      },
      {
        "question": "oculus",
        "answer": "eye",
        "example": "oculist"
      },
      {
        "question": "iateria",
        "answer": "medical healing",
        "example": "podiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "metron",
        "answer": "measurement",
        "example": "optometrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "geras",
        "answer": "old age",
        "example": "geriatrics"
      },
      {
        "question": "soma",
        "answer": "body",
        "example": "psychosomatic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "disease",
        "example": "osteopath"
      },
      {
        "question": "odontos",
        "answer": "tooth",
        "example": "exodontist"
      },
      {
        "question": "pous, podus",
        "answer": "foot",
        "example": "octopus, podium"
      },
      {
        "question": "cheir (chiro-)",
        "answer": "hand",
        "example": "chirography"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "RecognizeRoot",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "graphein",
        "answer": "to write",
        "example": "graphology"
      },
      {
        "question": "kallos",
        "answer": "beauty",
        "example": "calligrapher"
      },
      {
        "question": "pyge",
        "answer": "buttock",
        "example": "callipygian"
      },
      {
        "question": "kakos",
        "answer": "harsh, ugly, bad",
        "example": "cacophony"
      },
      {
        "question": "senex",
        "answer": "old",
        "example": "senescent"
      },
      {
        "question": "anthropos",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "example": "anthropology"
      },
      {
        "question": "astron",
        "answer": "star",
        "example": "astronomy"
      },
      {
        "question": "nautes",
        "answer": "sailor",
        "example": "astronaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "ge (geo-)",
        "answer": "earth",
        "example": "geology"
      },
      {
        "question": "zoion",
        "answer": "animal",
        "example": "zodiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "lingua",
        "answer": "tongue",
        "example": "bilingual"
      },
      {
        "question": "philein",
        "answer": "to love",
        "example": "philadelphia"
      },
      {
        "question": "biblion",
        "answer": "book",
        "example": "bibliophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "autos",
        "answer": "self",
        "example": "autonomous"
      },
      {
        "question": "socius",
        "answer": "companion",
        "example": "asocial"
      },
      {
        "question": "notus",
        "answer": "known",
        "example": "notorious"
      },
      {
        "question": "summus",
        "answer": "highest",
        "example": "consummate"
      },
      {
        "question": "vetus",
        "answer": "old",
        "example": "inveterate"
      },
      {
        "question": "genesis",
        "answer": "birth",
        "example": "congenital"
      },
      {
        "question": "chronos",
        "answer": "time",
        "example": "chronic"
      },
      {
        "question": "pathos",
        "answer": "feeling",
        "example": "empathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "grex, gregis",
        "answer": "herd, flock",
        "example": "egregious"
      },
      {
        "question": "sciens",
        "answer": "knowing",
        "example": "prescient"
      },
      {
        "question": "omnis",
        "answer": "all",
        "example": "omniscient"
      },
      {
        "question": "nomos",
        "answer": "law, order, arrangement",
        "example": "metronome"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "SameOrOpposite",
    "data": [
      {
        "first_word": "egoistic",
        "second_word": "altruistic",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "misanthropic",
        "second_word": "philanthropic",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "misogamous",
        "second_word": "polygamous",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "dexterous",
        "second_word": "skillful",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "sinister",
        "second_word": "threatening",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "optical",
        "second_word": "visual",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "notorious",
        "second_word": "infamous",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "consummate (adj.)",
        "second_word": "unskilled",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "chronic",
        "second_word": "acute",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "glib",
        "second_word": "halting",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "ophthalmologist",
        "second_word": "oculist",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "geriatric",
        "second_word": "pediatric",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "endodontist",
        "second_word": "exodontist",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "calligraphy",
        "second_word": "cacography",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "astronaut",
        "second_word": "cosmonaut",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "biopsy",
        "second_word": "autopsy",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "dichotomous",
        "second_word": "cut in two",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "congenital",
        "second_word": "hereditary",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "first_word": "veteran",
        "second_word": "\"old hand\"",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "first_word": "anachronous",
        "second_word": "timely",
        "answer": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "dislikes women",
        "answer": "misogynist"
      },
      {
        "question": "is pathologically self-interested",
        "answer": "egomaniac"
      },
      {
        "question": "studies the development of the human race",
        "answer": "anthropologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "is an expert on insects",
        "answer": "entomologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "collects books",
        "answer": "bibliophile"
      },
      {
        "question": "mounts and stuffs animal skins",
        "answer": "taxidermist"
      },
      {
        "question": "is an eye doctor",
        "answer": "ophthalmologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "is a student of linguistics",
        "answer": "philologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "has \"split off\" from reality",
        "answer": "psychotic"
      },
      {
        "question": "commits antisocial acts without guilt or pangs of conscience",
        "answer": "psychopath"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "delivers babies",
        "answer": "obstetrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats female ailments",
        "answer": "gynecologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats infants",
        "answer": "pediatrician"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats skin diseases",
        "answer": "dermatologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats skeletal deformities",
        "answer": "orthopedist"
      },
      {
        "question": "is a heart specialist",
        "answer": "cardiologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats mental or emotional disturbances",
        "answer": "psychiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats disorders of the nervous system",
        "answer": "neurologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats minor ailments of the feet",
        "answer": "podiatrist"
      },
      {
        "question": "treats ailments of the gums",
        "answer": "periodontist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "ruthless; without conscience",
        "answer": "unconscionable"
      },
      {
        "question": "suspiciously fluent or smooth",
        "answer": "glib"
      },
      {
        "question": "outstandingly bad; vicious",
        "answer": "egregious"
      },
      {
        "question": "out of place",
        "answer": "incongruous"
      },
      {
        "question": "study of the family tree; speciality of tracing ancestry",
        "answer": "genealogy"
      },
      {
        "question": "science of heredity",
        "answer": "genetics"
      },
      {
        "question": "in correct order of time",
        "answer": "chronological"
      },
      {
        "question": "socially awkward",
        "answer": "gauche"
      },
      {
        "question": "record of heart action",
        "answer": "cardiogram"
      },
      {
        "question": "equally skillful with both the right and left hand",
        "answer": "ambidextrous"
      },
      {
        "question": "social scientist who deals with the problems of aging",
        "answer": "gerontologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "extrasensory perception",
        "answer": "telepathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "branch of dentistry specializing in the care of children's teeth",
        "answer": "pedodontia"
      },
      {
        "question": "blood-pressure apparatus",
        "answer": "sphygmomanometer"
      },
      {
        "question": "growing old (adj.)",
        "answer": "senescent"
      },
      {
        "question": "palm reader",
        "answer": "chiromancer"
      },
      {
        "question": "that which arouses sexual desire",
        "answer": "aphrodisiac"
      },
      {
        "question": "representation of the whole",
        "answer": "epitome"
      },
      {
        "question": "diseased; pertaining to the study of disease (adj.)",
        "answer": "pathological"
      },
      {
        "question": "measurement of time",
        "answer": "chronometry"
      },
      {
        "question": "hostility; strong dislike; aversion",
        "answer": "antipathy"
      },
      {
        "question": "to occur, or cause to occur, at the same time or rate",
        "answer": "synchronize"
      },
      {
        "question": "ignorant",
        "answer": "nescient"
      },
      {
        "question": "knowledge of an occurence beforehand",
        "answer": "prescience"
      },
      {
        "question": "enjoying being with the herd; liking companionship",
        "answer": "gregarious"
      },
      {
        "question": "to identify strongly with the feelings of another",
        "answer": "empathize"
      },
      {
        "question": "instrument to measure atmospheric pressure",
        "answer": "barometer"
      },
      {
        "question": "to separate from the herd",
        "answer": "segregate"
      },
      {
        "question": "possessed of shapely buttocks",
        "answer": "callipygian"
      },
      {
        "question": "ugly, illegible handwriting",
        "answer": "cacography"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Matching",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "disparage",
        "answer": "play down"
      },
      {
        "question": "equivocate",
        "answer": "purposely talk in such a way as to be vague and misleading"
      },
      {
        "question": "titillate",
        "answer": "tickle; stimulate pleasurably"
      },
      {
        "question": "adulate",
        "answer": "flatter lavishly"
      },
      {
        "question": "proscribe",
        "answer": "prohibit"
      },
      {
        "question": "obviate",
        "answer": "make unnecessary"
      },
      {
        "question": "militate",
        "answer": "work against"
      },
      {
        "question": "malign",
        "answer": "slander"
      },
      {
        "question": "condone",
        "answer": "forgive"
      },
      {
        "question": "placate",
        "answer": "change hostility to friendliness"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "YesNo",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Do you normally disparage something you admire?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you equivocate if you think it unwise to take a definite stand?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do pleasant things titillate you?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do emotionally mature people need constant adulation?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Is sugar proscribed for diabetics?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a substantial fortune obviate financial fears?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Does a worker's inefficiency often militate against his keeping his job?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Do people enjoy being maligned?",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "question": "Do we generally condone the faults of those we love?",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Can you sometimes placate a person by apologizing?",
        "answer": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "FillInTheBlank",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "You've been asked to take a stand on a certain issue, but you don't have the courage to be either definitely for or against.",
        "answer": "equivocate",
        "blank": "You _"
      },
      {
        "question": "You spread around an unpleasant story that you know will blacken someone's reputation.",
        "answer": "malign",
        "blank": "You _ that person."
      },
      {
        "question": "Your friend is justifiably angry-you asked him to go to a party with you, ignored him all evening, and then finally left with someone else. What must you do if you wish to restore the relationship?",
        "answer": "placate",
        "blank": "You must try to _ him."
      },
      {
        "question": "You virtually worship your therapist. You express your admiration in lavish flattery; you praise her in such excessive terms that she appears devoid of all human frailty.",
        "answer": "adulate",
        "blank": "You _ her."
      },
      {
        "question": "You are crowding 260 on the scales, so your doctor warns against high-calorie meals, rich desserts, second helpings, excessive carbohydrates, etc.",
        "answer": "proscribes",
        "blank": "The doctor _ these foods."
      },
      {
        "question": "You child Johnnie has smacked the neighbor's kid-entirely without provocation, you are forced to admit. But after all, you think, tommorow the other kid will, with equal lack of provocation smack Johnnie.",
        "answer": "condone",
        "blank": "You _ Johnnie's behavior."
      },
      {
        "question": "When your son, understandably expecting praise, mentions the three B's and two A's he earned in his courses, you respond, callously, \"Is that the best you can do? What stopped you from getting all A's?\"",
        "answer": "disparage",
        "blank": "You _ his accomplishment."
      },
      {
        "question": "You have run out of cash and plan to go to the bank to make a withdrawl; then unexpectedly you discover a twenty-dollar bill you secreted in your desk drawer months ago.",
        "answer": "obviates",
        "blank": "Your find _ a trip to the bank."
      },
      {
        "question": "You are the soul of honesty, but unfortunately, you have a sneaky, thievish, sinister look-and no one ever trusts you.",
        "answer": "militates",
        "blank": "Your appearance _ against you."
      },
      {
        "question": "The centerfold of Playboy or Playgirl provides a mild and agreeable stimulation.",
        "answer": "titillates",
        "blank": "The centerfold _ you."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Recall",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "change hostility into friendliness",
        "answer": "placate"
      },
      {
        "question": "make unnecessary",
        "answer": "obviate"
      },
      {
        "question": "belittle",
        "answer": "disparage"
      },
      {
        "question": "overlook or forgive a transgression",
        "answer": "condone"
      },
      {
        "question": "tickle; delight; stimulate pleasurably",
        "answer": "titillate"
      },
      {
        "question": "spread malicious rumors about",
        "answer": "malign"
      },
      {
        "question": "purposely use language susceptible of opposite interpretations",
        "answer": "equivocate"
      },
      {
        "question": "act to disadvantage of",
        "answer": "militate"
      },
      {
        "question": "forbid",
        "answer": "proscribe"
      },
      {
        "question": "worship; flatter fulsomely",
        "answer": "adulate"
      }
    ]
  }
]